現場の遺体は　二係の山門屋執行官
The body found at the crime scene
was Enforcer Yamatoya from Division 2.
The enforcement
was performed by a Dominator,
ドミネーターによる執行だが
and the one who shot him
was Inspector Shisui, also from Division 2.
撃ったのは　同じ二係の酒々井監視官
Mizue Shisui
After the enforcement,
she took Yamatoya's Dominator
執行後　山門屋のドミネーターを持ち去り　消息を絶った
and disappeared.
An Inspector went missing...
監視官が消えた
To be honest,
I have no idea what's going on.
正直　訳が分からん
So this is all we have to
go on for now, huh?
現時点で　手掛かりはこいつだけか
WC...
「ＷＣ？」
If I keep having things taken away from me, I'm gonna lose my mind
Ubaware tsuzukeru nara mou kurutte shimau yo
奪われ続けるなら
もう狂ってしまうよ
This endless "end" will make me stop breathing
Owari no nai "owari" ni boku wa iki wo shinaku natte
終わりの無い「終わり」に僕は息をしなくなって
Enigmatic Feeling
Why do they have to take things away from me? I'm about to fall apart
Ubawanakya ikenai no? Mou hodokete shimau yo
奪わなきゃいけないの
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
The world began to melt
Sekai ga tokedashite
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
God descended to confront and ask me
Kami-sama ga orite kite boku ni tsukitsuketa
神様が降りて来て
僕に突きつけた
"Who are you?"
I freed myself by walking in the divide of this world broken into two
Futatsu ni wakareta sekai ni sotte jibun wo hanatta
２つに分かれた世界に沿って
自分を放った
Is there only one God in such a fine borderline?
Kamihitoe darou kamihitoe darou kyoukaisen kami wa hitori na no?
紙一重だろう　紙一重だろう
境界線　神は１人なの
I'm gonna lose my mind, I'm gonna lose my mind...
Okashiku natte okashiku natte
おかしくなって おかしくなって
Suddenly I'll find myself taking you away
Fui ni kimi wo ubatte shimau no darou
ふいに君を奪ってしまうのだろう
Crazy! Crazy!
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
Because my heart can't focus
Pinto no awanai kokoro ni
ピントの合わない心に
Shake me! Shake me!
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I can't even look into the mirror
Kagami sae mo nozokenai
鏡さえも覗けない
#2: The Creeping Unknown
隐匿渐近的虚实
Akira Yamatoya
Regarding our approach to capturing
the bomber the other day and the results...
先日の　爆弾魔確保に至るまでの工程と結果
I wrote up a report with my observations
along with what I think we did wrong.
考察と問題点を　私なりにまとめました
Please submit it to the Chief.
局長に提出を　お願いします
The focus of this report
is not appropriate.
見出しがよくないな
The report you wrote is about
an Inspector who deviated from her duty.
君が書いたのは　業務を逸脱した監視官についての報告書だろう
Mr. Ginoza, I put in some
words about you, too.
宜野座さん　あなたについても　記述させてもらいました
To think that you,
an Enforcer,
執行官である　あなたが
pointed a Dominator
at another Enforcer from Division 2...!
二係の執行官に　ドミネーターを向けるだなんて
Following the book doesn't
always give the best results.
模範的な行動が　常に最良の結果を　もたらすとは限らないことも
You should keep that in mind.
知っておいた方がいい
I'm not asking for opinions
from an Enforcer.
執行官の意見など　聞いていません
You may want to relax a little,
Inspector Shimotsuki.
少し　肩の力を抜いたらどうですか　霜月監視官
Mr. Ginoza was an Inspector, too.
宜野座さんも　元は監視官
His opinions are based on experience
and can definitely come in handy.
彼の経験からくる意見　きっと　役に立ちます
Yayoi...
弥生さん…
It's precisely because he quit being
an Inspector that I won't listen to him.
監視官であることをやめたなら　なおさら　聞く気はありません
Yeah, I think
this is a good report.
とても　よく　まとまってると思う
Are you sure about this?
いいのか
I gave you permission to use it,
使用許可を出したのは　私だから
宜野座さんが　処罰されることはありません
so you won't be
punished for it, Mr. Ginoza.
I'll go question Kitazawa.
私は　喜汰沢の聴取に向かいます
Who's doing the Holo analysis
on the crime scene?
現場のホロの分析は誰が？
I am.
私がやっていますが
Then, Mr. Hinakawa,
please take over that work.
じゃあ　それは　雛河さんが引き継いでください
You want Hinakawa to do it...?
雛河に？
You can do it, right,
Mr. Hinakawa?
やれるよね　雛河さん
Yes... I can.
やれる…　です
Ms. Shimotsuki, please
work with the others
霜月さんは　みんなと一緒に　現場に残されたメッセージの解読を
to decode the message
left at the crime scene.
こっちの指示は　任せたわね
I'll leave matters
here to you, okay?
Inspector Tsunemori!
常守監視官
Akira Kitazawa,
your Crime Coefficient suddenly rose
喜汰沢旭　あなたの犯罪係数は
right after the fourth
bombing incident the other day.
先日の４度目の犯行直後に　急激に上昇した
But normally,
it's not possible.
でも　通常　そんなことはあり得ない
あなたはこれまで　どうやって　サイコパスをクリアに保ってたの？
How did you keep your Psycho-Pass
clear all this time? Answer the question.
答えなさい
何が　おかしいの？
What's funny?
My Hue is clear.
It can't get clouded.
奇麗だ　俺の色相　濁るわけがない
I've always been clear.
俺は　ずっと奇麗なんだ
It's thanks to him.
He always helps me out.
ありがとう　あの人はいつだって俺のために…
ああ　最高だよ
He's the best.
"He"?
あの人？
ホロで　人質を偽装してまで公安を誘い出した理由は　何だ？
Why did you go so far as to use
a Holo to fake taking a hostage
in order to lure out
the MWPSB?
Huh?
Holo? What're you talking about?
ホロって　何言ってんだ
I'm talking about the hologram you used
to make us think you took a hostage.
お前が人質に見せ掛けた　ホログラムのことだ
No! That was him!
違う　あれは　あの人だ
He made me clear!
I'll fight the world with him!
俺を　クリアにしてくれた
俺は　あの人と一緒に　世界と闘うんだ
お話にならないわね
We're getting nowhere.
We did question him, too,
but it was the same.
こちらでも聴取を行ったけど　同じよ
He kept raving on and on about
that imaginary accomplice of his.
実在しない共犯者についての妄言ばかり
He must be mentally ill.
病気ね
Raving...
妄言…
Since the cymatic scan
didn't detect anyone,
サイマティックスキャンに　反応がなかった以上
it's not possible that
there was someone else there.
他の誰かがいたなんて　あり得ないわ
Did you find out anything
about Inspector Shisui?
酒々井監視官については　何か分かりましたか？
It's strange.
Although it comes and goes,
妙なのよね　断続的ではあるけど
we have been able to track her
whereabouts using GPS,
ＧＰＳで　彼女の行方は　追跡できているし
and her Dominator has stayed online
and is still properly authenticated.
ドミネーターも　正常に認証されたまま　オンラインを維持している
In other words, Inspector Shisui's actions
are approved by Sibyl.
つまり　酒々井監視官の行動は　シビュラに容認されていると
禾生局長も　そう判断しているわ
Chief Kasei thinks so, too.
Shisui isn't doing
anything illegal
酒々井は　何ら違法性のある　行動は取っておらず
and is conducting an investigation
that Sibyl acknowledges.
現在も　シビュラの認識下で　捜査を行っている
確かに　ドミネーターの反応を信じるなら
If we are to trust the Dominator's response,
that must be what's going on.
そういうことに　なるんでしょうね
You're saying that Enforcer Yamatoya's
enforcement was also appropriate?
山門屋執行官も　正当に執行したと？
山門屋が　逃亡を企てたのかもしれない
He might've tried to run.
That's more than enough reason for enforcement.
十分な　執行理由になるわ
Then why did Inspector Shisui
have to disappear?
では　なぜ　酒々井監視官は姿を消したんでしょうか？
She might've had
to act secretly.
秘密裏に行動する必要があったのかもしれない
That might've been why
she left a message.
だから　彼女は　私たちにメッセージをよこした
WC...
「ＷＣ？」
Right.
そう
青柳さん　本当に　そう思ってるんですか？
Do you really think that's
what happened, Ms. Aoyanagi?
Well, do you have
any other ideas?
じゃあ　他に　どう考えろというの？
もしも…
What if...
Hm?
What if there was someone else,
besides the MWPSB, there...
もしも　あの現場に　公安以外の何者かがいたとしたら
What if this person shot Mr. Yamatoya
and wrote that message...
その何者かが山門屋さんを撃ち　メッセージを書いたとしたら
Don't tell me... you believe
what Kitazawa said?
まさか　喜汰沢のこと信じるの？
可能性の話です
I'm saying it's possible.
There's no such thing as a person
who can't be seen by the Sibyl System.
シビュラシステムにも　見えない人間なんているはずないでしょ
透明人間を捜すなんて　私の仕事じゃないわ
Searching for ghosts...
...isn't in my job description.
一番最初に浮かぶのは「Water　Closet」　水洗トイレだよな
The first thing that comes to mind
is "water closet," isn't it?
Huh?! Most people
would think "World Cup"!
「World　Cup」でしょ　普通
It could be "wild caught," too.
「Wild　Caught」っていう　線もあるわね
Artificially-bred wild animals, huh?
人工飼育された　野生動物か…
But that wouldn't make sense.
だが　意味が通らない
だったら　トイレもおかしいでしょ
Says the guy who thinks
it means "restroom"?!
What's the point of writing
restroom on a wall?!
何で　わざわざ　壁にトイレ？
Maybe you gotta go?
Then go on, no one's stopping you!
行きたいの？行けばいいじゃん
Hey, I didn't write it.
俺に言うな
You need to do more than watch
if you want to ease your stress... Inspector.
見ているだけじゃ　気分は晴れませんよ
監視官
喜汰沢への聴取の立ち会い　許可してくれて　ありがとうございます
Thank you for giving me permission
to join you when you questioned Kitazawa.
本来　俺を関わらせないのが　定石なのに
Normally, the rules wouldn't
allow me to take part in it.
東金財団の話？
Are you talking about
the Togane Foundation?
Yes. As I'm sure
you're aware,
ええ　あなたは知っているはずだ
OW Pharmaceutical,
which was hurt by Kitazawa,
喜汰沢の被害に遭った　ＯＷ製薬
is run by the Toganes...
my relatives.
その会社を経営しているのが　東金…　俺の親族だと
あなたは　感情で　判断を間違う人間には見えない
You don't seem the type that allows
emotions to cloud your decisions.
だから　リスクより
So I focused more on the benefits,
rather than the risk,
あなたを同行させることのプラス要素を　考慮させてもらいました
of taking you along with me.
You were a therapist,
weren't you, Mr. Togane?
セラピストだったんですね　東金さん
俺の経歴を見た上での判断　というわけですか
So you made that decision
considering my background, huh?
You're quite perceptive
about people.
あなたは　よく人を見ている
This is... amazing...
これ…　すごい
You left the Holo verification
to Hinakawa
雛河に　ホロの検証を任せたのも
in order to make use
of his background as a Holo designer.
元ホロデザイナーという　あいつの経歴を　生かしてのことだった
That's just natural.
I am your boss, after all.
まあ　そのくらいは
一応　上司ですから
何ですか？
What is it?
透明人間は実在する
The ghost exists.
俺も　そう思います
I think so, too.
There's no proof.
I also know that it's not that easy
確証はありません
サイマティックスキャンや　ドローンによる捜査を欺くのが
to deceive cymatic scans
and Drones.
容易じゃないことも　分かっています
Even so, it still doesn't appear
that Kitazawa is delusional.
それでも　喜汰沢が妄言を吐いているようには見えない
To start with, it's hard to think
that someone like Kitazawa
そもそも　彼のようなタイプが単独犯とは考えにくい
would commit a crime alone.
そう　誰かが　裏で糸を引いている
Right. There's someone
pulling the strings behind him.
Otherwise, it doesn't
make much sense.
そうでなければ　おかしい
I-Inspector...
か…監視官
What's the matter, Mr. Hinakawa?
雛河さん　どうしたの？
That Holo is amazing!
このホロ…　すごいよ
確かに　これはなかなか手の込んだ作りね
Yeah, the design
is incredibly elaborate.
外見の情報量が膨大過ぎ
It uses a massive amount of data
to define its appearance.
If you're just trying
to deceive people looking at it,
見る人を　だますだけなら
you don't have to use
this many layers.
こんなに　レイヤー　重ねなくていい
You can actually create
such a sophisticated Holo?
そこまで　精巧なホロを　作れるものなの？
If you have a model, yes.
モデルがいれば
Ms. Karanomori.
唐之杜さん
On it.
はいはいっと…
I can't find her in the Ministry
of Welfare's database.
厚生省のデータベースには　入ってないわね
Right. It's hard to use
an existing person.
そう　現存する人は　使いにくい
They could bump
into each other.
鉢合わせする可能性もある
But if it's someone
who's not alive...
だけど　生きていない人なら
死亡被害者か
A dead victim, huh?
Okay. Let me switch
to searching a different database.
ＯＫ　検索先を変えてみるわ
特徴が一致する人物が　一人いる
There's one person
whose characteristics match.
Maki Shimizu
１５年前の飛行機事故で亡くなった　女の子ね
It's a girl who died
in an airplane accident fifteen years ago.
Not too shabby, Sho.
翔君　お手柄じゃない
でも　待ってください
Hold on. The girl who died
was eight years old at the time.
亡くなった女の子　当時　８歳って…
Maki Shimizu
Yeah, that Holo doesn't really look
like an eight-year-old, does she?
８歳には見えないわね
To sum it up, this Holo was a result
of taking a dead person and determining...
要するに　このホロは死人を成長させたものだってこと
１５年後の今　もし　生きていたらっていう設定でね
...what she would look like
if she was alive today, fifteen years later.
This is strange.
おかしい　いくら何でも手の込みようが異常だわ
No matter how you look at it,
this is way too elaborate.
Maybe they're the type
who wants to go all the way?
やるなら　とことんって　タイプなんじゃない
You see that type more often
than you might think.
案外いるわよ　そういうの
Inspector Tsunemori.
Where are you right now?
常守監視官　今どこに
I'm in the Analysis Lab.
Did something happen?
分析室です　何かあったんですか
Kitazawa's Crime Coefficient has...
喜汰沢の犯罪係数が　執行対象外まで　下がったわ
...gone down so low that
he's no longer a target for enforcement.
How could this...?
こんなことが…
Yeah. To see a Crime Coefficient
that had risen to the level
ああ　一度　執行対象まで上昇した犯罪係数が
for enforcement actually
go down this low...
ここまで下がるなど…
It's unprecedented, huh?
過去に前例がない…　か
It's thanks to him.
あの人のおかげだ
He came to see me.
He made me clear.
あの人が会いに来てくれた　クリアにしてくれた
面会記録を
Let's check the visitors record.
I've already done it.
What he's saying is a lie.
もう調べたわ　でたらめよ　こいつの言ってること
According to the security video,
the only one who visited him
監視カメラの映像によると　面会に来たのは
公安局直属医療機関のセラピスト一人だけ
was a therapist from
the MWPSB's medical agency.
There was no one else.
他には誰も来てないわ
Can I talk to that therapist?
そのセラピストと話せますか
It's been a while.
久しぶりですね
Under normal circumstances,
I couldn't really face you.
本来はあなたに合わせる顔はないんですが…
Well, it wasn't your fault.
いえ　先生に責任はありませんよ
喜汰沢に行った　セラピーの内容と
Could you tell us what kind
of therapy you gave Kitazawa?
Also, did you notice
anything unusual?
何か　変わった点などがあれば　教えていただけますか
I simply provided
my usual services.
私は通常どおりの業務を行ったにすぎません
You'll see if you check
the security cameras.
監視カメラを見ていただければ　分かりますよ
Indeed... Right.
確かに…　そうですね
You look very tired.
Maybe you're overworked.
だいぶ　お疲れのようですね　働き過ぎかな
You lack both sleep and rest.
You need some relaxation.
睡眠　休息　共に不足している　リフレッシュも必要ですよ
Yes, but that's
easier said than done.
ですよね…
でも　なかなか　難しくて
Also, this advice is outside my field,
but smoking harms your health.
それと　これは　専門外のアドバイスですが
喫煙は　健康を害します
Keep it in moderation.
ほどほどに
This is unprecedented.
前代未聞ね
To think that we're
transferring a culprit
あれだけの事件を起こした犯人を一般医療施設に移送なんて
who committed such serious crimes
to a general medical facility...
We have no choice since
his Psycho-Pass became clear.
サイコパスが　クリアになった以上　仕方ない
そういう規定だ
Those are the rules.
Inspector Tsunemori, why did you
leave his transfer to Division 2,
先輩　一係が挙げた犯人なのに
when we, Division 1,
are the ones who captured him?
どうして移送を二係に任せたんですか
Sorry. I want to go
home early today.
ごめん　今日は早めに上がるつもりなの
Huh?!
A therapist scared me by saying that
my Psycho-Pass would get clouded.
セラピストに脅されちゃったんだ　サイコパスが濁るぞって
I'll finish the report
by tomorrow.
報告書は　あしたまでに　まとめておくから
Well then, see you tomorrow.
それじゃあ　お疲れさま
Oh, hey!
ちょっと
Once Kitazawa is in that facility,
he'll be out of our jurisdiction.
施設に入れば　喜汰沢は公安の管轄から外れてしまう
This transfer is the last
opportunity to question him.
この移送は　やつを取り調べられる最後のチャンスなんだ
I know.
That's exactly why...
分かってます　だからこそ…
Tsunemori is probably
considering Aoyanagi's feelings.
常守は　青柳の気持ちを酌んでやってるんだろう
Try to understand.
察してやれ
I wonder if this is enough
for the smell to stick on me...
これでも　におい　付いちゃうのかな
副流煙は健康を害しますよ
Secondhand smoke
is harmful to your health!
Give it a rest.
I know that.
うるさいな　分かってるわよ
Why don't we clean the room
for a change? It'll cheer you up.
たまには　部屋の掃除もしましょう　気分転換になりますよ
Okay, okay.
はい　はい
Oh? There's a scratch on the wall.
おや　壁に傷がついてますね
Would you like me
to contact a repairman?
補修業者に連絡しますか
A scratch?
傷
Yeah.
This can't be happening!
そんなはずない
先輩　喜汰沢が逃亡しました
Inspector Tsunemori!
Kitazawa escaped!
It happened
in the Tama Area's KT Building.
現場は　多摩地区　ＫＴビル
When Division 2 asked him
where he made the bombs,
二係が　喜汰沢に　爆弾の製造場所を尋ねるところ
he showed them
to a rental office in the building.
ビルの一室にある　レンタルオフィスに　案内されました
There, he hurt Inspector Aoyanagi
with a knife he hid in that room
そこで　喜汰沢は部屋に隠していたナイフで青柳監視官を負傷させ
and left with the bombs he had prepared.
He's currently still on the run.
用意していた爆弾を所持したまま　現在も逃亡中です
Inspector Aoyanagi...
青柳監視官…
No way... Someone
with a clear Psycho-Pass could...
嘘よ　サイコパスがクリアな人間が…
We imposed a traffic restriction in the area
and advised residents to evacuate.
周辺一帯に交通規制をかけ　住民に避難勧告を出しました
Considering the amount of time
that's passed since the incident,
経過時間から考えて
Kitazawa is still likely
to be in the area.
喜汰沢は　まだ　その範囲内に　とどまっていると考えられます
There's a narrow alley
behind the building.
ビル　裏側の細い路地
Down that alley
is an entrance to the sewers.
その先に　下水路への進入口があるわね
Yes. But it's locked.
はい　でも進入口はロックされています
He can't use it.
使用することはできません
What if it was
unlocked beforehand?
あらかじめ　ロックが　解除されていたとしたら
That's not possible.
There's a scanner at the entrance.
あり得ません
進入口には　スキャナーがあります
If someone gets close to it,
they will definitely be detected.
誰かが　事前に近づいてきたら　必ず　察知できるはずです
I see Kitazawa at the sewer entrance.
Looks like it was unlocked.
下水路への進入口で　喜汰沢を発見
ロックは　解除されていたみたいね
Can't be! How?!
そんな…どうやって
More importantly,
we should follow him.
それより　追跡を…
We are too far away
from the location.
ここからでは　難しい距離だな
We'll take care of it.
こちらで対処します
Is this Tsunemori?
常守か
You guessed Kitazawa's escape route?
読んでいたんですか　喜汰沢の逃走ルート
It's hard to think that
he could come up with a plan
移送中に逃亡するなんて計画を　一人で考えつくとは思えない
to escape during the transfer
all by himself.
Moreover, he was in custody.
There's no way he could've prepared a weapon.
ましてや　収容されていた彼が　凶器を用意できるはずがない
In other words...
つまり…
There's no doubt that
someone gave Kitazawa
喜汰沢に逃走を指示して　下準備を行った誰かが必ずいる
instructions on how to escape
and made preparations...
...someone who has the means
to evade cymatic scans.
サイマティックスキャンを　かいくぐる手段を持った誰かが
And this person
is challenging the MWPSB.
そして　その人物は　公安局に挑戦している…
I... I...
俺は…　俺は…
そこまでよ
Stop right there!
Don't come near me!
I set another bomb!
来るな　また爆弾を仕掛けた
If you come any closer than that,
I'll let it go off!
それ以上俺に近づくなら　爆発させる
No...
駄目よ
もう　諦めなさい
Just give up now.
You think I'm lying, right?
嘘だと思ってるんだろ…
Damn you...
You keep mocking me...!
チクショー…　なめやがって
Stop it!
やめなさい
This is...
これは…
I've got one more bomb.
爆弾は　もう一つある
He went to a lot of trouble
to help me escape.
せっかく　あの人が　逃がしてくれたんだ
So I have to go.
俺は　行かなきゃいけないんだ
You too said that
I wasn't wrong, right?! So...!
あんただって言っただろ　俺は間違ってないって…　だから
That may have been the case...
until you pressed that button.
そうかもしれなかった
スイッチを押すまでは
Crime Coefficient is 357.
「犯罪係数　３５７」
Lethal Eliminator.
「リーサル・エリミネーター」
監視官　発砲許可を
Inspector, please give me
permission to shoot.
Sorry, Kamui... After you went
to the trouble of making me clear...
ごめんよ…　鹿矛囲…
せっかく　クリアにしてくれたのに
Kamui?
カムイ
Who's that?
誰
Hey, tell me...
what color am I now?
なあ　教えてくれよ…
俺は　今　何色なんだ
What color?
何色
Yeah, right now you're
the color of raw sewage.
そうね　ドブみたいな色ね
I see...
I get it now...
そうか…　分かった
メッセージの意味
...what that message means...
How foolish
the Public Safety Bureau is...
愚かな公安局
He could've been made clear again.
彼は　クリアにできた
He still could've been saved.
まだ　救えた…
All is calm, all is bright
Akane Tsunemori...
常守朱
A whispering fallen angel
Sasayaku tenshi wa ochite
囁く天使は堕ちて
I had hoped that
you would understand.
君なら分かると期待したのに…
Gently devours you, body and soul
Yasashiku hamu wa anata no subete o
優しく食むわ　あなたの全てを
It's my guilty
You notice me
Kidzuku
気づく　目を見開いてる
With your eyes wide open,
Me o mihiraiteru
A faint blue as lifeless as concrete
Honoaoi konkuriito
仄青い混凝土
In a cold tone,
Tsumetaku watashi o
冷たく私を
Call my name and give me a kiss
And then hold me in the arms of the empty shell that is your body
Soshite dakishimete anata no inai sono karada de
そして抱きしめて
あなたのいないその体で
That soul that you've cast out
Hakidashita sono inochi wa
吐き出しその生命は
Has not yet completely vanished
Mada katachi o nokoshiteiru wa
まだ形を残しているわ　紅く
I glimpse a vivid red eternity
Akaku azayaka na eien ga miete
鮮やかな永遠が見えて
It starts singing right next to me
Tonari de sore wa utaidasu
隣でそれは歌いだすわ
What was I born for
ねえ　私を愛して
Come on, love me
Nee watashi o aishite
Because I won't let you go
Hanasanai kara
離さないから
Hello my name is
A world where humans' state of mind
and the tendency of their personalities can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls
are commonly called 'Psycho-Pass.'
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations
that appear in the show are fictitious,
and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.